In this video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company
and the market cap of the company is ₹163, 1000 crore,
P Russia is 4956 and the company gives a debt ratio of 0.62
percent
and if we talk about the positive points in the company, then the
company has reduced its debt and the
company is almost debt free, the
result of the company is expected to be good in the next quarter
and the
dividend payout of the company is now at this point in the year and if we
talk about the negative points, then
in the last two-three years the holding of promoters has
reduced by 7.83 percent
and now let's also see the profit of the company,
1049 crore, 1194 crore, 1473 crore, 1271
crore, this time it has been seen in the profit of the company
and in the share holding, the holding of promoters is
4804, Rafi Building 26.2876
and the public holding is 11.34
and at this time the share price is ₹1200 and ₹
12 per share is ₹100  It is supported and at this time
641 juice is present in the food and this hair had gone
smoothly, at this time it is
available at discount, if you want to buy from this company
then you
can buy it for Rs. 1200 only, that's all
in this video, if you liked the information given in the video
then set an alarm for the video,
share it and subscribe to our channel.